This demonstration Should be performed on virtual machine LON-DC1 logged on with username Contoso\Administrator and password Pa$$w0rd

1. Go to Start then point to All Programs, then Accessories, then Windows PowerShell, and then click on Windows PowerShell to open Windows PowerShell

2. Click the Control Box in the upper-left corner of the window, and then click Properties

3. Configure various options for the Font, Layout, and Color tabs. Close the Properties dialog and review the changes you made.
  
Try several different configurations, and complete with a configuration that makes the shell comfortably viewable.