This demonstration Should be performed on virtual machine LON-SVR2 logged on with username Contoso\Administrator and password Pa$$w0rd

1. On the Start menu, point to Administrative Tools and then click on Server Manager

2. Click Features in the left-hand tree view

3. Click Add Features

4. Check "Windows PowerShell Integrated Scripting Environment (ISE)"

5. Click the "Add Required Features" button to continue through the wizard and Click Next

6. Click Install and complete the Wizard

7. On the Start menu, point to All Programs, then Accessories, then Windows PowerShell, and then click on Windows PowerShell ISE

8. Point out the three right-most toolbar buttons, which change the viewing panes. There are three panes:
   - Script
   - Command line
   - Output
   
